#### Contact

karlward97@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/karl-ward-239667171 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

C++

Visual Studio

OpenGL

# Karl Ward

Games Programmer at Feral Interactive

Bournemouth, United Kingdom

## Summary

Games Software Engineering (BSc) student at Bournemouth University achieving 1st class (81.6%) overall in my first year. I am a highly skilled programmer using C++ and C# in environments such as Visual Studio and Unity with a consistent professional approach to projects and a keen eye for well-structured and robust programming. Confident communicator and experienced with working in a team, developed through years participating in game-jams and developing game projects.

## Experience

Feral Interactive
Games Programmer
July 2019 - Present
London, United Kingdom

Bournemouth University
PAL Leader
September 2018 - June 2019 (10 months)
Bournemouth, United Kingdom

At my university I have taken the role of a PAL leader which includes the primary role of facilitating learning and engaging with a group of first year students. In this position I must create and present a lesson plan on a weekly basis, demonstrating my punctuality to deadlines and my independence when presenting and engaging with the class.

#### Tesco

Customer Service Assistant August 2016 - June 2019 (2 years 11 months)

In this job I have developed the interpersonal skills of working with a team and executing a task with a specific goal. Customer satisfaction is always a priority for creating a great shopping experience.

FreeFromWight
Lead Developer
May 2018 - March 2019 (11 months)
Bournemouth, United Kingdom

Worked as the lead developer on a developing a dining app with the creators of FreeFromWight. This is created using Xamarin using my knowledge of C# to create the functionality and implement the design that I've been provided.

## Education

Bournemouth University (2017 - 2021)

Petroc (North and Mid Devon)
BTEC Level 3 Diploma, IT and Computing (2014 - 2016)

Petroc (North and Mid Devon)
BTEC Level 2 Diploma, IT and Computing · (2013 - 2014)

Pilton Community College
GCSE's - ICT, Resistant Materials, System and Control · (2008 - 2013)